A Guide to the League of Women Voters of Montgomery County, Virginia Records, 1961-2001
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Voters service, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 10-43)
- Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 14-2)
- Memos, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 14-4)
- Regional Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 14-6)
- Agriculture, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 10-44)
- Catalogues, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 10-45)
- Facts for Voters pamphlets, 1986-1996 (Box-folder 10-46)
- Treasurer records, bank statements, returned checks, phone bills, deposit slips, 1987 (Box-folder 11-1)
- Phone bills, deposit slips, returned checks, 1987 (Box-folder 11-2)
- Education Fund, Safe Drinking Water, 1987 (Box-folder 11-3)
- LWV bulletins, 1987 (Box-folder 11-4)
- Newspaper articles on Mail Trolley, 1987 (Box-folder 11-5)
- Meeting basic human needs, Montgomery County, 1987 (Box-folder 11-6)
- Correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 14-7)
- State Convention, 1987 (Box-folder 14-8)
- State and Local Grant Guidelines, 1987 (Box-folder 14-10)
- Treasurers report, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 11-7)
- FY Board, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 11-8)
- Meeting Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 14-12)
- Bulletins from meetings, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 11-10)
- Fiscal, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 11-9)
- LWV bulletins, 1988 (Box-folder 11-11)
- Treasurer records, phone bills, receipts, statements, returned checks, 1988 (Box-folder 11-12)
- Receipts and bills, 1988 (Box-folder 11-13)
- LWV Office Log, 1988 (Box-folder 11-26)
- Thank You Letters, 1988 (Box-folder 14-13)
- Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 11-14)
- Virginia Legislative directory pamphlet, 1988-1995 (Box-folder 11-15)
- Membership handbook and information, 1988-1996 (Box-folder 11-16)
- Receipts, phone bills, deposit slips, 1989 (Box-folder 11-17)
- League of old town hall for the LWV, 1989 (Box-folder 11-18)
- A study of the Juvenile Justice system in Montgomery County, 1989 (Box-folder 11-19)
- LWV Calendar, 1989 (Box-folder 11-27)
- Phone bills, receipts, paid bills, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 11-28)
- Paid bills, deposit slips, treasurer reports, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 11-29)
- LWV handbooks, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 11-20)
- Information about elementary schools and high schools in Montgomery County, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 11-21)
- Bulletins from meetings, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 11-22)
- Minutes from meetings, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 11-23)
- School Study Material, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 14-20)
- Voting in VA pamphlets and other information, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 11-24)
- LWV Calendar, 1990 (Box-folder 11-30)
- Treasurer's reports, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 11-31)
- Phone bills, receipts, paid bills, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 11-32)
- Bank statements, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 11-33)
- Health care, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 11-34)
- Minutes, agendas, budgets, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 11-35)
- Health programs, adult day care, 1991 (Box-folder 11-36)
- LWV Calendar, 1991 (Box-folder 11-37)
- Environmental management in Montgomery County's Karst Terrain, 1991 (Box-folder 11-38)
- Candidates Forum, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 11-25)
- State programs, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 11-39)
- Minutes study, legislative interview, bulletins, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 11-40)
- Facts for Voters, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 11-41)
- Bank statements, deposits, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 11-42)
- Phone bills, receipts, paid bills, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 11-43)
- Treasurer reports, meeting minutes, donations, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 12-1)
- LWV handbooks, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 12-2)
- Governor's Commission on Campaign Finance Reform, Government Accountability and Ethics, 1992 (Box-folder 12-3)
- Radford University Resource Guide, 1992 (Box-folder 12-4)
- Virginia--organization of state government, 1992 (Box-folder 12-5)
- LWV calendar, 1992 (Box-folder 12-6)
- LWC address lists, 1992 (Box-folder 12-7)
- Architectural Review Board Study, 1992 (Box-folder 14-21)
- Bank statements, CD statements, checking, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 12-8)
- LWV calendar, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 12-9)
- Board meeting minutes, agenda, memoranda, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 12-10)
- Bulletin, mailing list, finance drive, treasurer reports, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 12-11)
- Phone bills, receipts, paid bills, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 12-12)
- LWV bulletins, 1993 (Box-folder 12-13)
- Financing health care program, 1993 (Box-folder 12-14)
- Treasurers reports, 1993 (Box-folder 12-15)
- Subsidized housing in Pulaski, Va., 1993 (Box-folder 12-16)
- Renewal of membership, 1993 (Box-folder 12-17)
- Changing needs of Montgomery County school age children during the 90's, 1993 (Box-folder 12-18)
- "Smart Road," 1993 (Box-folder 12-19)
- LWV programs, 1993 (Box-folder 12-20)
- LWV calendar, 1993 (Box-folder 12-21)
- Reference book and directory, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 12-22)
- Programs, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 12-23)
- Bank statements, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 12-24)
- Phone bills, receipts, paid bills, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 12-25)
- Bank statements, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 12-26)
- Bulletins, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 12-27)
- Expenditures, balance book, deposit slips, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 12-28)
- Bulk rate mail fee information, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 12-29)
- Elected school boards and executive (private) sessions, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 12-30)
- Governor's Conference on Education, 1994 (Box-folder 12-31)
- LWV bulletins, 1994 (Box-folder 12-32)
- The Virginia Voter, 1994 (Box-folder 12-33)
- Hungarian women proposal, 1994 (Box-folder 12-34)
- LWV calendar, 1994 (Box-folder 12-35)
- Voting, 1994 (Box-folder 12-36)
- Board meeting minutes, 1994 (Box-folder 12-37)
- Bank statements, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 12-38)
- Phone bills, receipts, paid bills, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 12-39)
- Population coalition information, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 12-40)
- I-73: An Ongoing Controversy, 1995 (Box-folder 13-1)
- Agenda, meeting minutes, budgets, 1995 (Box-folder 13-2)
- Programs, 1995 (Box-folder 13-3)
- Campaign watch sheet, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13-4)
- Bank statements, deposits, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13-5)
- Budget, meeting minutes, membership, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13-6)
- Member handbook, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13-7)
- Phone bills, receipts, paid bills, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 13-8)
- Reconnecting the citizens to the community information, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 13-9)
- State Studies, 1995-2003 (Box-folder 14-19)
- Education fund, 1996 (Box-folder 13-10)
- Resolution presented to the delegates at the 1996 Convention and lake Michigan inter-league group, 1996 (Box-folder 13-11)
- Bulletins, agendas, meeting minutes, 1996 (Box-folder 13-12)
- Presentation to LWV breakfast, 1996 (Box-folder 13-13)
- Long term health care, 1996 (Box-folder 13-14)
- Minutes, studies, bulletins, 1996 (Box-folder 13-15)
- Bulletins and other publications, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 13-16)
- Meeting Agendas, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 14-14)
- Special Services program, 1997 (Box-folder 13-17)
- Consensus, 1998 (Box-folder 13-18)
- Robert Stuart's award materials, 1998 (Box-folder 13-19)
- League Handbook, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14-1)
- National, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14-36)
- State Women's League, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14-37)
- Health Care, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14-38)
- Membership, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14-39)
- Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14-40)
- Voter Services, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14-41)
- Letters, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14-42)
- Budget, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14-43)
- Board Agendas/Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 14-44)
- Virginia League of Women Voters, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 14-45)
- U.S. League of Women Voters, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 14-46)
- Programs/Publicity, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 14-47)
- Letters, Misc., 1999-2000 (Box-folder 14-48)
- General Documents, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 14-49)
- Mailing Materials, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 14-50)
- Documents, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 14-35)
- Programs/Publicity, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 14-34)
- United States League, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 14-33)
- Virginia League, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 14-32)
- Board Agendas/Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 14-31)
- Voter Publications, 2001 (Box-folder 14-23)
- LWV Calendar/Agenda/Minutes, 2001 (Box-folder 14-24)
- Action/Positions, 2001 (Box-folder 14-25)
- Budget, 2001 (Box-folder 14-26)
- Program/Study, 2001 (Box-folder 14-27)
- Bulletin, 2001 (Box-folder 14-28)
- Bulletin, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 14-22)
- Bulletin, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 14-52)
- Bulletins, Fall 2001 (Box-folder 14-53)
- Agendas, 2001 (Box-folder 14-54)
- Meeting minutes/mailing materials, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 14-51)
- Directory, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 14-29)
- LWV Voter's Workshop. (Box-folder 13-20)
- Montgomery County Public Schools pamphlet. (Box-folder 13-21)
- Pamphlets: Guide to Blacksburg, Area Recycling Centers. (Box-folder 13-22)
- Action Correspondence US Congress. (Box-folder 13-23)
- National Program for Action--International Relations Development--Trade UN. (Box-folder 13-24)
- National Program for Action: National Resources. (Box-folder 13-25)
- National Program--Concurrence Public Policy on Reproductive Choices. (Box-folder 13-26)
- Education Fund. (Box-folder 13-27)
- National Program for Action Human Resources/ Social Policy. (Box-folder 13-28)
- Office lease agreement. (Box-folder 13-29)
- Requests. (Box-folder 13-30)
- Order forms. (Box-folder 13-31)
- Poverty study, interviews of social workers. (Box-folder 13-32)
- Index cards with different information. (Box-folder 13-33)
- League survey for Blacksburg residents. (Box-folder 13-34)
- Volunteer Emergency Foster Care of VA. (Box-folder 13-35)
- Finance job descriptions. (Box-folder 13-36)
- Overseas education program--National Program Fund. (Box-folder 13-37)
- State Program for Action, State Finances. (Box-folder 13-38)
- State publications. (Box-folder 13-39)
- Handbook for Local League Leaders. (Box-folder 13-40)
- Guide for Discussion Leaders. (Box-folder 13-41)
- Pamphlets on promoting and developing study circles on critical social and political issues. (Box-folder 13-42)
- "Celebrating Women" and "Celebrating Girls" clothing options. (Box-folder 13-43)
- Groundwater use. (Box-folder 13-44)
- Video instructions. (Box-folder 13-45)
- Address labels. (Box-folder 13-46)
- Bulletins. (Box-folder 13-47)
- Parliamentary Procedure. (Box-folder 14-30)
- Headquarters Lease Agreement. (Box-folder 14-11)
- VHS Tapes (Box 15)
  - Preference Voting Tape, 1996
  - I-73: An On-Going Controversy Tape, 1995
  - League of Women Voters Broadcast Video, 1990
  - What is the State of Public Education in Virginia?, 1990s
  - 1995 Candidates Forum Video, 1995
  - LWV Educational Fund 1996 Candice Bergen PSA, 1996
  - LWV Educational Fund Phylicia Rashad PSA, 1996
  - Excerpts From LWV Lynchburg City Council Candidates Forum, 1992
  - Three on Proportional Representation NBC News Tape, 1994
  - LWV Training Teleconference Video 1989
  - LWV Open Government...Executive Sessions, How do they Fit? Tape, 1990s
  - How New Budget Priorities Will Affect Local Services, 1990s
  - Tools for Drinking Water Protection Video, 1990s
  - Saphar & Associates PSA "Keep it Clean" Video, 1990s
  - Poverty- W. Reform, 1990s
  - Montgomery County Poverty and Welfare Reform: A Money Saver or a People Saver, 1990s
  - LWV Take Back the System Video, 1992
  - 1996 Forum at Blacksburg Municipal Building Video, 1996
  - LWV Fixing Virginia's Tax Structure: A Call for Reform! Video, 1990s
  - The Power to Protect Groundwater Video, 1990s